liteneasy.com.au 2007-12-26

# Lite n' Easy - Privacy Policy

|  |  |  |  |  |   
  |   |    
|  |   
|   | Introduction |    
  |   |    
  |   | At Lite n' Easy we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any personal information we collect about you is used to provide you with the best possible product and service based on your individual needs and to keep you informed of any additional services we may offer which may be relevant to you. For the purpose of this document the terms "we", "our" and "us" refer to Lite n' Easy and it's related companies. |   |   |   |    
  |   |    
|  |   
|   | How we collect the information |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

We may collect personal information about you when you deal with us over the telephone, send us correspondence (whether by letter, fax or email), visit our web site or when you have contact with us in person (including agents or contractors to Lite n' Easy such as delivery drivers). At no time does Lite n' Easy collect any information from our customers other than that information that our customers voluntarily give us.

|   |   |   |    
  |   |    
|  |   
|   | The information we collect and how we use it. |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

When you purchase products from Lite n' Easy we may need to collect some or all of the following details in order to fulfil your purchases:  

|  |   
---|---  
| Full name and address  
| Contact telephone number/s  
| Delivery instructions  
| Payment details such as credit card information  
| Email address  
| Date of birth  
| Sex  
| Height and weight  
| Any medical conditions, such as diabetes, which may be effected by the type of product we sell you  
| Any food allergies or dislikes you may have  
| Your reasons for starting Lite n' Easy  
| Your weight loss goals  
| Any feedback relating to your use of the Lite n' Easy program (for example, the amount of weight you lose while on the program)  
  
Aside from using this information to fulfil your purchase request, we may also use it to occasionally notify you about new products, promotions, and relevant information which we think you will find valuable. You have the option to decide how you receive these types of communications (for example by mail, email or telephone). You also have the option not to receive these types of communications. For more information please refer to our "Choice and Opt-out" section below. 

From time to time we may also request information via market research, surveys or contests. Your participation in any of these is optional. The information is collected in order to continually improve the services we offer you. In most cases the information you supply will be used on an aggregated basis only. 

  |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Disclosure of personal information to third parties. |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

We may disclose relevant personal information to third parties when necessary. For example your delivery details will be shared with our contracted delivery drivers. 

Other than for the above, we will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing or any other purpose without your prior consent, unless required by law. 

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Choice & Opt-out |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

You may request at anytime to have your personal information updated if you no longer wish to receive some or all of the communications we regularly send to our customers such as newsletters, product information and specials. You may also change the method by which you receive these communications (for example, receiving the newsletter by email rather than normal mail). To change your preferences simply write to us, phone us or email us at [privacy@liteneasy.com.au](mailto:privacy@liteneasy.com.au).

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Access to and correction of information |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

You may request access to or have corrections made to the personal information we hold about you simply by writing to us, phoning us or emailing us at privacy@liteneasy.com.au .

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Cookies |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

A cookie is a piece of data containing information about you. It is stored on your hard drive and is used for a number of reasons. If, for example, you use the ordering system on the Lite n' Easy web site, you have the option to store the details you enter such as your name and address. This will save you having to re-enter the same information the next time you use the ordering page. Cookies, and in some cases IP addresses, also enable us to track and target the interests of our users and how they navigate around our site, which in turn enables us to enhance the features that are most popular with our users.

You may choose to set your computer so that it does not accept cookies. However, some parts of our site may not function properly if you do.

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Links |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

The Lite n' Easy website contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that Lite n' Easy is in no way responsible for the privacy policies of these other sites or companies. We encourage you to investigate the privacy policy of any other company or web site before disclosing any personal information with them.

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Security |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

The Lite n' Easy web site takes every precaution possible to protect your personally identifiable information. This includes the use of Firewalls and encrypting sensitive information using Secure Socket Layers (SSL) whenever appropriate.

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Changes to our Privacy Policy |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

We may amend this privacy policy as our business requirements or the laws change. Any changes to this privacy policy will be updated on the Lite n' Easy web site.

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   | Contacting Lite n' Easy |    
  |   |    
  |   | 

If you wish to gain access to your information, have a query relating to this privacy policy or feel your privacy has been breached please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator through any of the following means -

Email: [privacy@liteneasy.com.au](mailto:privacy@liteneasy.com.au)

Post: Privacy Policy Administrator  
Lite n' Easy  
PO Box 320  
Northgate QLD 4013

Telephone: **13 15 12**

|   |   |   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |    
|  |   
|   |    
  |   |   |   |   |   |
